<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<website theme='2fsec'>
   <title>Byethost</title>
   <style>

   </style>
   <page type='page' language='EN'>
      <name> Home</name>
      <image></image>
      <contents>
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.classifiedsadboard.com/index.php?referid=emrickj&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.classifiedsadboard.com/images/468-60.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Free Ads Posting&quot; style=&quot;display: block;margin: auto&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Sign up today with one of my affiliates, Byethost, for their premium hosting service. &amp;nbsp;I have been using Byethost for quite some time and I really enjoy using it. &amp;nbsp;They have been recently awarded &quot;Best Premium Hosting&quot; provider. &amp;nbsp;For more details, click on the following link:&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.ifastnet.com/?p=46&quot;&gt;http://blog.ifastnet.com/?p=46&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Also, you can activate a free SSL signed SSL certificate on any domain added into your cPanel. &amp;nbsp;Once you activate SSL, you will also benefit instantly&amp;nbsp;from the new superior HTTP/2 webserver protocol. &amp;nbsp;For more details, click on the following link:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.ifastnet.com/?p=39&quot;&gt;http://blog.ifastnet.com/?p=39&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To see some of the fabulous benefits you receive when you sign up for their premium hosting service, &lt;a href=&quot;?p=2&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary btn-sm&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;?p=2&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-outline-primary&quot; style=&quot;float: right;&quot;&gt;Next Page&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
      </contents>
   </page>
   <page type='page' language='EN'>
      <name>Features</name>
      <image></image>
      <contents>
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#3F51B5&quot;&gt;Some of the many premium hosting benefits and features:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;hr id=&quot;ht&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa fa-lg&quot;&gt;➀&lt;/span&gt; Free SEO and marketing tools:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Get in Google&lt;/b&gt; – The best way to submit your website into Google search engine, directly from cPanel in a few clicks.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEO Tools and Tip&lt;/b&gt; – 100’s of intelligent tools that analyze your sites search engine place, page titles and content so you can optimize your site for the highest position in Google for the keywords you are targeting.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;One-Click Site-Map&lt;/b&gt; – Creating a site map of every page and link on your site allows Google to discover ALL of your sites pages and add it into Google search engine, this One-Click Site-Map tool does all the heavy lifting for you by scanning your entire site and building the Site-Map list file!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Negative Review Scanner&lt;/b&gt; – Never has it been easier to automatically track and find negative reviews about your site, giving you the chance to learn from a review and talk directly back to your customers.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;2&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa fa-lg&quot;&gt;➁&lt;/span&gt; Premium hosting email&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;fa-ul&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa-li fa&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Unrestricted SMTP, POP, IMAP, PHP SendMail, WebMail and email client support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa-li fa&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Auto responders, Forwarders, Spam filters, Encryption and Mailing lists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa-li fa&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Full email account support allowing you to make email addresses at all your domains to send and receive any way you prefer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;3&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa fa-lg&quot;&gt;➂&lt;/span&gt; Statistics and logs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;As a Web-Master you will know the value of logs and statistics on your site, they help you learn about your visitors, where they come from, what they are clicking or downloading and much more, this information helps you improve your sites layout, content, promotions and partnerships or link exchanges you have on sites that are bringing traffic / visitors to you.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;On premium hosting you get awesome stats and logs:&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;fa-ul&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa-li fa&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Detailed visitor logs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa-li fa&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;AwStats&lt;/b&gt; – One of the best statistics applications available showing graphs, ordered summaries of your visitors, bandwidth, traffic sources and much more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa-li fa&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Webalizer&lt;/b&gt; – Another great statistic application that brings a wealth of invaluable information about your visitors and what they are doing on your site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa-li fa&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Script activity and CPU, connections&lt;/b&gt; – Specific information on which scripts your hosting account are running, showing which scripts are using the most resources that are running slowly, helping you find bad plugins or scripts that may need removing or optimizing to make your site run awesomely fast.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;4&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa fa-lg&quot;&gt;➃&lt;/span&gt; Security and encryption.&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Free SSL / HTTPS for all domains on premium hosting – We are one of only a few Web-hosts in the world that offer you the ability FOR FREE to enable a trusted SSL certificate on every domain in your hosting cPanel! &amp;nbsp;Not only is this free for all domains, it is super easy to enable by simply clicking LETS ENCRYPT icon in your premium cPanel, then click one button to enable SSL/HTTPS on your domain, it's that simple!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Site Lock&lt;/b&gt; – Our own custom in-house created security module for cPanel: &amp;nbsp;Site Lock allows you to lock the files you have uploaded to the server so they can't be deleted, modified or renamed by anyone, including hackers or similar. &amp;nbsp;This unique to iFastNet feature is a superb way to protect your files from unauthorised access or changes which are becoming more and more common online today, where hackers try to penetrate insecure or out of date scripts that are vulnerable. Our Site Lock keeps you safe!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Web Application Firewall&lt;/b&gt; – This is one of the hidden jewels with our premium hosting. &amp;nbsp;It runs on your premium server automatically detecting and blocking malicious traffic and bots from accessing your site or trying to login. &amp;nbsp;Every day we block 100,000’s of hacking attempts by bots trying to exploit your scripts / website.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;5&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa fa-lg&quot;&gt;➄&lt;/span&gt; Free RailGun by CloudFlare&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;A CloudFlare business plan costs 200.00 USD per month which includes the amazing RailGun system.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Our premium hosting allows you to use RailGun COMPLETELY FREE ! &amp;nbsp;Yes no cost at all!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;That is right, RailGun is free and included with every one of our premium hosting plans. &amp;nbsp; RailGun is a special service created by CloudFlare which integrates with CloudFlare hosting company partners who we are and has allowed us to install RailGun inside our premium hosting servers. &amp;nbsp;We can communicate with CloudFlare servers in a special way via RailGun that accelerates web pages upto 200x faster!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;You can learn more about RailGun here if you wanted to know more technical details :&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.ifastnet.com/?p=1&quot;&gt;http://blog.ifastnet.com/?p=1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;6&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;fa fa-lg&quot;&gt;➅&lt;/span&gt; Free domains, super fast servers, unlimited space, unlimited traffic and much more!&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;All of our premium plans include a free domain and in some cases 20 extra bonus free domains as well!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Unlimited space, traffic and file sizes are just some of the great features you get from premium, our enhanced premium plans have so many extra features there are just too many to list here.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;?p=1&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-outline-primary&quot;&gt;Previous Page&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;?p=3&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-outline-primary&quot; style=&quot;float: right;&quot;&gt;Next Page&lt;/a&gt;
      </contents>
   </page>
   <page type='page' language='EN'>
      <name>Sign Up</name>
      <image></image>
      <contents>
&lt;div&gt;I hope you have found this information useful for when you sign up for their premium hosting service.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
To see premium shared hosting offers, &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;https://ifastnet.com/portal/aff.php?aff=25010&amp;amp;pr=premo&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary btn-sm&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;To see business class hosting offers, &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;https://ifastnet.com/portal/aff.php?aff=25010&amp;amp;pr=busi&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary btn-sm&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;To see VPS server offers, &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;https://ifastnet.com/portal/aff.php?aff=25010&amp;amp;pr=vps&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary btn-sm&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;To register a domain name, &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;https://ifastnet.com/portal/aff.php?aff=25010&amp;amp;pr=domains&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary btn-sm&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;To see WHM Reseller plans, &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;https://ifastnet.com/portal/aff.php?aff=25010&amp;amp;pr=whmreseller&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary btn-sm&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;To see Dedicated Server plans, &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;https://ifastnet.com/portal/aff.php?aff=25010&amp;amp;pr=ded&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary btn-sm&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;To go to Budget Hosting solutions, &lt;a rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; href=&quot;https://ifastnet.com/portal/aff.php?aff=25010&amp;amp;pr=bud&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary btn-sm&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;?p=2&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-outline-primary&quot;&gt;Previous Page&lt;/a&gt;
      </contents>
   </page>
   <page type='page' language='EN'>
      <name></name>
      <image></image>
      <contents>

      </contents>
   </page>
   <page type='page' language='EN'>
      <name></name>
      <image></image>
      <contents>

      </contents>
   </page>
   <page type='page' language='EN'>
      <name></name>
      <image></image>
      <contents>

      </contents>
   </page>
</website>
